<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jae Logan</title>
    <link>http://jrliv.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jae Logan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 16:06:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jrliv.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Pull Request</title>
      <link>http://jrliv.com/post/my-first-pull-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 16:06:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jrliv.com/post/my-first-pull-request/</guid>
      <description>In this post I want to share my experience submitting my first pull request and contributing to open source. Honestly, my contribution wasn’t planned at all. It just kind of happened. I knew about open source software and how the idea worked but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to actually use git and attempt to submit a pull request to fix an issue on GitHub. The actual process itself turned out to be easier than I thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Variables in C#</title>
      <link>http://jrliv.com/post/working-with-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 22:26:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jrliv.com/post/working-with-variables/</guid>
      <description>One of the first things most new programmers learn how to do is work with variables. In this post I will discuss the different types of variables in C# and describe what they are, why they are used, and how to use them.
If you are already setup with Visual Studio or MonoDevelop on your computer, you can follow along with the post and run or modify the code snippets on your own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started Using C# Without Visual Studio</title>
      <link>http://jrliv.com/post/get-started-using-csharp-without-visual-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 17:22:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jrliv.com/post/get-started-using-csharp-without-visual-studio/</guid>
      <description>This post will show you how to get started using the C# programming language without installing Visual Studio or any other IDE. C# is a great programming language to learn for anyone new to programming.
Regardless of the language, most fundamentals behind programming can be practiced and learned using only a text editor and the command line. Using the command line to compile and run code provides a faster way for new programmers to get going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://jrliv.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 13:39:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jrliv.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello my name is Jae. I&amp;rsquo;m a Computer Science student and an aspiring developer. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken courses and dabbled in various languages and frameworks over the last few years but never stayed committed to becoming an experienced developer. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to recommit myself and my goal is to become a full stack .NET developer.
I will use this website to show my work as well as document and share everything I learn in the form of blog posts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>