<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iis on Jae Logan</title>
    <link>https://jrliv.com/tags/iis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Iis on Jae Logan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 12:23:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jrliv.com/tags/iis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Differences Between Sites, Applications, and Virtual Directories in IIS</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/differences-between-site-app-virtual-dir-iis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 12:23:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/differences-between-site-app-virtual-dir-iis/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using IIS 10 regularly over the last 2 years now and one thing that&amp;rsquo;s always confused me was the differences between sites, applications, and virtual directories and what they&amp;rsquo;re used for.
After doing some research on these components, I found that the easiest way to understand them from a high-level, is to think of them all as sort of a hierarchy of containers for each other. A site contains one or more applications, an application contains one or more virtual directories, and a virtual directory maps directly to a folder location on the disk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Redirect to Another URL Path in IIS</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/redirect-to-another-url-in-iis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 20:28:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/redirect-to-another-url-in-iis/</guid>
      <description>In a few steps this post will show how to use HTTP Redirect in IIS to specify rules that can redirect requests to another file path or website.
Prerequisites  Windows operating system Internet Information Services (IIS)  Steps  Open IIS. In the left pane under &amp;lsquo;Sites&amp;rsquo;, select the Web site or application that you want to redirect from.
 Double click on &amp;lsquo;HTTP Redirect&amp;rsquo; in the main pane under the &amp;lsquo;IIS&amp;rsquo; section:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>