<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jae Logan</title>
    <link>https://jrliv.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jae Logan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:39:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jrliv.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Operators in C#</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/working-with-operators/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:39:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/working-with-operators/</guid>
      <description>Working with operators is an important part of learning how to program. Every programming language uses operators. You will need to use them in essentially every program you write. Therefore every programmer will have to learn how to use them.
In this post I will write about operators in C# and show examples of how to work with some of them.
What is an operator? An operator is a special character that allows you to process and perform different mathematical or logical operations on data types and objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Programming Language Should I Learn First?</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/what-programming-language-should-i-learn-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 10:48:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/what-programming-language-should-i-learn-first/</guid>
      <description>I just wanted to write a quick post about my opinion of which programming language new developers should learn first. This question is so common. If you are a new developer, you might be trying to figure this question out right now. For some, this question can turn into a hurdle that they&amp;rsquo;re never able to jump over. It can be a critical question.
Trust me when I say you aren&amp;rsquo;t alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Pull Request</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/my-first-pull-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 16:06:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/my-first-pull-request/</guid>
      <description>In this post I want to share my experience submitting my first pull request and contributing to open source. Honestly, my contribution wasn’t planned at all. It just kind of happened. I knew about open source software and how the idea worked but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to actually use git and attempt to submit a pull request to fix an issue on GitHub. The actual process itself turned out to be easier than I thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Variables in C#</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/working-with-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 22:26:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/working-with-variables/</guid>
      <description>One of the first things most new programmers learn how to do is work with variables. In this post I will discuss the different types of variables in C# and describe what they are, why they are used, and how to use them.
If you are already setup with Visual Studio or MonoDevelop on your computer, you can follow along with the post and run or modify the code snippets on your own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started Using C# Without Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/get-started-using-csharp-without-visual-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 17:22:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/get-started-using-csharp-without-visual-studio/</guid>
      <description>This post will show you how to get started using the C# programming language without installing Visual Studio or any other IDE. C# is a great programming language to learn for anyone new to programming.
Regardless of the language, most fundamentals behind programming can be practiced and learned using only a text editor and the command line. Using the command line to compile and run code provides a faster way for new programmers to get going.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>