<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dotnet on Jae Logan</title>
    <link>https://jrliv.com/tags/dotnet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dotnet on Jae Logan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 14:46:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jrliv.com/tags/dotnet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Missing Start Without Debugging Option</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/visual-studio-missing-start-without-debug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 14:46:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/visual-studio-missing-start-without-debug/</guid>
      <description>One issue I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced with Visual Studio a few times over the years is when the &amp;lsquo;Start Without Debugging&amp;rsquo; option under the Debug menu decides to disappear. I have no clue what causes this or what I&amp;rsquo;m doing to make the option hide from me. I can always still use Ctrl + F5 to run my project without debugging, but for some reason it bothers me when the option is missing so here are two ways to add it back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned from .NET Conf 2020</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/dotnet-conf-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:46:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/dotnet-conf-2020/</guid>
      <description>Source: .NET Conf 2020
Last week .NET Conf 2020 happened. Taking place November 10th-12th, the conference celebrated 10 years as a virtual event for developers. This year was the first time I was able to watch most of the sessions in a timely manner so I decided to highlight what I learned.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, .NET Conf is a free, 3-day virtual developer event, co-organized by Microsoft and the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Redirect to Another URL Path in IIS</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/redirect-to-another-url-in-iis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 20:28:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/redirect-to-another-url-in-iis/</guid>
      <description>In a few steps this post will show how to use HTTP Redirect in IIS to specify rules that can redirect requests to another file path or website.
Prerequisites  Windows operating system Internet Information Services (IIS)  Steps  Open IIS. In the left pane under &amp;lsquo;Sites&amp;rsquo;, select the Web site or application that you want to redirect from.
 Double click on &amp;lsquo;HTTP Redirect&amp;rsquo; in the main pane under the &amp;lsquo;IIS&amp;rsquo; section:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started Using C# Without Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://jrliv.com/post/get-started-using-csharp-without-visual-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 17:22:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrliv.com/post/get-started-using-csharp-without-visual-studio/</guid>
      <description>This post will show you how to get started using the C# programming language without installing Visual Studio or any other IDE. C# is a great programming language to learn for anyone new to programming.
Regardless of the language, most fundamentals behind programming can be practiced and learned using only a text editor and the command line. Using the command line to compile and run code provides a faster way for new programmers to get going.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>